export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: '1 + 1 = ?',
    options: ['0', '1', '2', '3'],
    answer: '2'
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: '25 + 24 = ?',
    options: ['0', '1', '2', '49'],
    answer: '49'
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: '1 + 0 = ?',
    options: ['0', '1', '2', '3'],
    answer: '1'
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '18 + 15 = ?',
    options: ['0', '1', '2', '33'],
    answer: '2'
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '51 + 1 = ?',
    options: ['0', '1', '52', '3'],
    answer: '52'
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: '1 + 10 = ?',
    options: ['110', '11', '2', '3'],
    answer: '11'
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '2 + 3 = ?',
    options: ['0', '5', '2', '3'],
    answer: '5'
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '1 + 87 = ?',
    options: ['0', '1', '88', '3'],
    answer: '88'
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: '1 + 2 = ?',
    options: ['0', '1', '2', '3'],
    answer: '3'
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: '9 + 1 = ?',
    options: ['0', '1', '2', '10'],
    answer: '10'
  },
];

export const players = [
  { name: 'Bob John', score: 50 },
  { name: 'Stephen Chong', score: 40 },
  { name: 'Apple Bottom', score: 10 },
];